(function(){const i=document.createElement("link").relList;if(i&&i.supports&&i.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const e of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))u(e);new MutationObserver(e=>{for(const t of e)if(t.type==="childList")for(const c of t.addedNodes)c.tagName==="LINK"&&c.rel==="modulepreload"&&u(c)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function a(e){const t={};return e.integrity&&(t.integrity=e.integrity),e.referrerpolicy&&(t.referrerPolicy=e.referrerpolicy),e.crossorigin==="use-credentials"?t.credentials="include":e.crossorigin==="anonymous"?t.credentials="omit":t.credentials="same-origin",t}function u(e){if(e.ep)return;e.ep=!0;const t=a(e);fetch(e.href,t)}})();const r=[{questionText:"What is by far the most utilized punch in boxing?",answerOptions:["The cross","The jab","The hook"],correctAnswer:"The jab"},{questionText:"When does a boxer become undisputed champion in his/her weightclass?",answerOptions:["When she/he has aquired 50 wins in their respective weightclass","When she/he has aquired the IBF, WBO, WBA and WBC belts","When she/he has aquired the IBF, WBO, WBA, WBC and WTT belts"],correctAnswer:"When she/he has aquired the IBF, WBO, WBA and WBC belts"},{questionText:"What did former champion Vasyl Lomatjenkos dad make him do for 4 years before he could start training boxing?",answerOptions:["Swimming, to give him an advantage in back strength, core strength and endurance","Ukranian folk dance, to give him an advantage in his footwork","Wrestling, to give him an advantage in overall strength and mental prowess"],correctAnswer:"Ukranian folk dance, to give him an advantage in his footwork"},{questionText:"Which one of these boxers were heavyweight champion of the world at one point in their career?",answerOptions:["Jimmy Young","Michael Bentt","Ron Lyle"],correctAnswer:"Michael Bentt"},{questionText:'What preferred offense does a "Muay khao" fighter use?',answerOptions:["His/her knees","His/her hands","His/her elbows"],correctAnswer:"His/her knees"},{questionText:'Who is the only muay thai boxer who has won "Sports Writers of Thailand Fighter of the Year" three years in a row?',answerOptions:["Samart Payakaroon, 1981 - 1983","Panpayak Jitmuangnon, 2013 - 2015","Petchboonchu FA Group, 2006 - 2008"],correctAnswer:"Panpayak Jitmuangnon, 2013-2015"},{questionText:"What stadium in Thailand is historically held with the highest regard when it comes to professional muay thai?",answerOptions:["Rajadamnern stadium in Bangkok","Bangla stadium in Phuket","Rawai stadium in Rawai"],correctAnswer:"Rajadamnern stadium in Bangkok"},{questionText:'What is a "Wai khru ram muay" and what does it represent?',answerOptions:["An armband which is worn throughout the fight which honors your respective gym and khru (trainer)","A ritualistic dance which is performed before a fight to show respect and gratitude to the parents, khrus (trainers), ancestors and the ring itself","A fighters last fight which is often more of a showing/spectacle combined with a speech to honor said fighters journey, krhus (trainers), gym and fans"],correctAnswer:"A ritualistic dance which is performed before a fight to show respect and gratitude to the parents, khrus (trainers), ancestors and the ring itself"},{questionText:"What was the first weightclass that irish fighter Conor McGregor became champion of while in the UFC?",answerOptions:["Featherweight","Welterweight","Lightweight"],correctAnswer:"Featherweight"},{questionText:"Several high ranked MMA fighters and champions descend from which well-known wrestling optimistic russian republic?",answerOptions:["Chechen Republic","Republic of Dagestan","Republic of Mordovia"],correctAnswer:"Republic of Dagestan"},{questionText:"Besides the UFC (Ultimate Fighting Championship), name one other well-known MMA organisations around the world",answerOptions:["Bellator MMA","Tukhgul MMA Championship","GSP Fighting Championship"],correctAnswer:"Bellator MMA"},{questionText:"Which fighter and champion has held the longest winningstreak ever in the UFC (Ultimate Fighting Championship)?",answerOptions:["Tony Ferguson, lightweight: 2013 - 2020","Anderson Silva, middleweight, light heavyweight: 2006 - 2013","Demetrious Johnson, flyweight: 2012 - 2018"],correctAnswer:"Anderson Silva, middleweight, light heavyweight: 2006 - 2013"}],g="Welcome! Please enter your name and proceed with the quiz!",d=document.querySelector("#gameDescription"),w=document.querySelector("#questionText"),p=document.querySelector("#answer1"),f=document.querySelector("#answer2"),y=document.querySelector("#answer3"),q=document.querySelector("#nextQuestionBtn");d.innerHTML=g;document.querySelector("#startGameBtn").addEventListener("click",b);document.querySelector("#restartBtn").addEventListener("click",k);document.querySelector("#nextQuestionBtn").addEventListener("click",l);p.addEventListener("change",h);f.addEventListener("change",h);y.addEventListener("change",h);document.querySelectorAll(".answer-radio").forEach(function(o){o.style.display="none"});let m="",n=0,s=0;r.sort(()=>Math.random()-.5);function b(){m=document.querySelector("#playerInput").value,d.style.display="none",document.querySelector("#playerDetails").style.display="none",document.querySelectorAll(".answer-radio").forEach(function(o){o.style.display="inline-block"}),l()}function h(o){const i=o.currentTarget.nextSibling.nodeValue;q.removeAttribute("disabled");const a=r[n].correctAnswer;i==a?s+=1:s-=1}function l(){if(n++,n>=r.length){A();return}w.innerHTML=r[n].questionText,document.querySelector('label[for="answer1"]').textContent=r[n].answerOptions[0],document.querySelector('label[for="answer2"]').textContent=r[n].answerOptions[1],document.querySelector('label[for="answer3"]').textContent=r[n].answerOptions[2],document.querySelector(".nextquestionbtn").style.display="inline-block"}function k(){document.querySelector("#questionContainer").style.display="block",document.querySelector("#pointsContainer").innerHTML="",document.querySelector("#gameOver").style.display="none",r.sort(()=>Math.random()-.5),s=0,n=0,l()}function A(){document.querySelector("#gameOver").style.display="block",document.querySelector("#questionContainer").style.display="none",document.querySelector("#pointsContainer").innerHTML=`Grattis, ${m}, du fick ${s} po\xE4ng!`}
